indiansavage.com 2015-04-08

# PRIVACY - Maggie Dallospedale Fashion diary

## Privacy

Maggie Dallospedale Fashion diary (the “Site”) takes your privacy seriously. This “ **Privacy Policy** ” describes what information is collected, and how it is used, when you visit the Site.  
The only personal information we collect is what you give us. When you leave a comment, or communicate with us by email, you may elect to give us personally-identifiable information such as your name, email address, geographic location, or other information which could be used to locate or contact you.  
Non-Personal Information Our website host, advertising network, advertisers, and affiliates (“Affiliates”) may collect non-personal information such as your IP address, the type of browser you are using, the referring website, the operating system you are using, your Internet service provider, the search terms you use on our Site, the specific web pages you visit, and the duration of your visits.  
Cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Cookies collect certain types of non-personal information such as the search terms you use on our Site, the specific web pages you visit, the duration of your visits, and your preferences. Maggie Dallospedale Fashion diary does not use cookies, but one or more of our Affiliates do. Please note that our Affiliates’ use of cookies is governed by their own privacy policies.  
Information Use: Our Affiliates may use non-personal information to help analyze site traffic, understand customer needs and trends, and carry out targeted promotional activities. They may use non-personal information by itself or aggregate it with information they have obtained from others to produce research reports and other information and data, and may share such information with third parties.  
Third-Party Advertising: We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on the Site. Those companies may use non-personal information about your visit to the Site to display ads for goods and services which may be of interest to you.  
Links to Other Sites: We may provide links to other websites from time to time. We are not responsible for the content or information use at any of those sites, and you should review each site’s privacy policy.  
Modification: We may amend or revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. Please review it periodically. Your continued use of the site after any change in this Privacy Policy will mean you accept such change.  
Contact If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at info (at) indiansavage (dot) com.  
Last Updated Oct 01, 2014
